<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Remco van Dijk</title>
    <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Remco van Dijk</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:38:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://rvandijk01.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HASC-V</title>
      <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/projects/hasc-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:38:24 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rvandijk01.github.io/projects/hasc-v/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on a RISC-V simulator in Haskell as a side project. You can find more information about it on the HASC-V github page.&#xA;At some point, I will write a proper article about it here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSc Thesis</title>
      <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/projects/msc-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 15:43:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rvandijk01.github.io/projects/msc-thesis/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently doing my Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis entitled:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Fault Injection Attacks on Trusted Execution for RISC-V Cores&amp;rdquo;&#xA;at the CAES group at the University of Twente.&#xA;Motivation&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;As the RISC-V Instruction Set Architecture (ISA) grows in popularity, it becomes a greater target for malicious behavior. When RISC-V cores are deployed in embedded systems (which is currently the main use case), there is often a need for facilitating secure firmware updates over the air, which can be achieved by Trusted Execution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Hugo Experience</title>
      <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/posts/hugo-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 16:13:13 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rvandijk01.github.io/posts/hugo-post/</guid>
      <description>What is Hugo?&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;To make this website, I have chosen to do it with Hugo. Hugo is a tool that allows you to automatically generate HTML/CSS/JavaScript code from a Markdown specification and a configuration file.&#xA;Why Hugo?&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;The reason is quite simple, I wanted to start a personal website as a side project, but dislike writing HTML/CSS/JavaScript &amp;lsquo;code&amp;rsquo;. Thus, I chose to use a tool like Hugo, since it makes the task of formatting web content trivial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my test post</title>
      <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/posts/mypost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:04:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rvandijk01.github.io/posts/mypost/</guid>
      <description>&#xD;Heading 1&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Heading 2&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Heading 3&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;Heading 4&#xD;Link to heading&#xD;module Cat (cat) where cat :: Cat cat = Cat { () } </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rvandijk01.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal website. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, you can find various articles and information here about myself, projects I&amp;rsquo;m doing (or have done in the past) and anything else that I might find interesting to put on here.&#xA;Note that this website is a work in progress. Between writing my Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis, working as a TA and my personal life, I try to allocate some time each day to various side projects (this website being one of them).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://rvandijk01.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rvandijk01.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>My preferred method of contact is my business email address.&#xA;My student email address is available for university-related communications, but keep in mind that soon I won&amp;rsquo;t have access to it anymore.&#xA;For other socials, please see the buttons on the main page.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
